OK.
The next thing I want to talk to you about is silence.
Yep, that was silent.
And what does that communicate?
Nothing.
Have you ever heard of, or given, or received the silent treatment?
Ah, we see it in relationships a whole lot.
And what the silent treatment is something like this.
"So, do you want to talk about it?"
No, I'd rather be silent and punish you, than tell you how I'm really feeling or thinking.
The silent treatment is a way in which we communicate.
It communicates that we don't want to communicate.
I cannot encourage you enough, not to give people the silent treatment.
And I've known a lot of people, I've worked with a lot of people in my life that love the silent treatment.
They love for you to have to figure out what it is that you're upset about.
And that is really, really bad in communication.
It is one of the worst non-verbal tools that you can pick up and use.
So, stop using the silent treatment and start encouraging yourself to use words, which is verbal communication, to communicate how you feel.